<help title="General" popup="yes">
These are general tips that you should read:

"/sCarReflect" to switch the car reflection
"/8bit" to switch the 8bit gfx
"/radialblur" to toggle the effect when you move. An short variant is avaible: /rb
"/svd [number]" to Set View Distance
"/sit" to... well, use them and you'll see
"/sBloom" to switch bloom

F1 for freeroam menu... lol
F4 to show/hide the iphone (youtube)

* Rhino takes damage from explosions, so watch out for RPGs and other tanks :D
* As you probably already know there are safes areas: no more spawnkill!
* You can save e spawn cars (check personal cars)
* The stats are already maxed out
* A modification of Vreload is active (Rhino, Hunter, Hydra cooldowns, Rhino different shooting system)
* Freeroam has gravity and gamespeed disabled, setting skin won't reset health, also the veh repair is disabled
* There is a mod called "glue": press x to stick to a vehicle!
* There are some cars' models overwritten: Andromada, AT-400, DFT-30, Barracks.

Make sure you check the other tabs too!

PS: this server has Dynamic IP: use filters in the server list or connect using the quick connect:
* mtasa://merottomirko.mynetgear.com:22003



It could be a bit time-consuming, but it's recommended to read the following list.
Here's some of the resources active here:

upgradestats 		--Max stats by default
personalcar 		--Save and load saved car
vreload 			--Rhino aiming system
iphone (youtube)	--F4 to youtube your favourite songs
tankdamage 			--Rhino get hurt by explosion
greenzone 			--Anti spawn kill (not vehs)
realdriveby 		--Default resource, here's active
paynspray 			--Some paynspray are open here!
foodshop 			--You can refill your health by buying food (despite the imgs it's free)
kwkchaticon 		--A phone will popup when u're chatting. The more msgs u sent the nice the phone
carreflect 			--/sCarReflect will show you what this is
regen 				--Health and armor auto regen!
8bit 				--/8bit to switch to 8bit gfx
glue 				--Press x to stick to a vehicle
heligrab 			--Don't drop!
yttheatre 			--Type /yt to choose the video to play while in the Astro drive-in cinema
drawtag 			--Let's spray some walls! See dedicated tab for help
cvehicle 			--Use /cveh to open vehs doors
VDistance 			--Use /svd to set you view distance (default: ~800)
nyancat 			--Use /nyan to switch. Modified version of the epic resource --buggy
newarea51gate 		--Area 51 gates now open!
shader_bloom_fix 	--Use /sBloom to switch bloom on/off
i_fps 				--If you want to see how many FPS do you have, then type /fps in chat. It can also be moved
helicopterrope		--Press 5 to drop a rope with which you can go down!
ferriswheel			--Hint: go to Santa Maria Beach
</help>
